In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to pronounce the AH as in FATHER vowel.
我们将学习如何发音 FATHER 中的 AH 元音。
This vowel needs a lot of jaw drop.
这个元音需要很大的下巴张开。
AH.
AH。
The tongue tip lightly touches behind the bottom front teeth,
舌尖轻轻触碰下前牙的后面，
and the back part of the tongue presses down a little bit.
舌头的后部稍微向下压。
AH.
AH。
The lips are neutral, very relaxed.
嘴唇是中性的，非常放松。
AH.
AH。
Because the tongue presses down in the back,
因为舌头在后部向下压，
you can see further into the dark space in the mouth.
你可以看到嘴里的黑暗空间更深。
Let's see that by watching this vowel up close and in slow motion.
让我们通过近距离和慢动作观看这个元音。
The lips are relaxed and the tongue is lowered in the back.
嘴唇放松，舌头在后部降低。
The inside of the mouth is dark.
嘴巴内部是黑暗的。
The word JOB.
单词 JOB。
The jaw drops,
下巴下垂，
and the tongue presses down in the back.
舌头在后部向下压。
AH.
AH。
When this vowel is in a stressed syllable,
当这个元音在重读音节中时，
the voice will go up and come down in pitch.
声音的音调会上升然后下降。
AH.
AH。
Job.
Job。
AH.
AH。
When it's in an unstressed syllable,
当它在非重读音节中时，
it won't be as long,
它不会那么长，
and it won't have the up-down shape of the voice.
也不会有声音的上升下降形状。
AH.
AH。
For example, in the word BLOCKADE.
例如，在单词 BLOCKADE 中。
AH.
AH。
BLOCKADE.
BLOCKADE。
Blinked lips and tongue pressed slightly down in the back.
嘴唇闭合，舌头在后部稍微向下压。
But because the pitch is flatter and the syllable is quicker,
但因为音调更平，音节更快，
it sounds unstressed.
听起来像是非重读。
Ah.
Ah。
Stressed AH.
重读 AH。
Job.
Job。
AH.
AH。
Unstressed AH.
非重读 AH。
Blockade.
Blockade。
AH.
AH。
Ah,
Ah，
ah,
ah，
ah, ah.
ah，ah。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Honest, ah,
Honest，ah，
honest.
honest。
Occupation, ah,
Occupation，ah，
occupation.
occupation。
Hot,
Hot，
ah,
ah，
hot.
hot。
Clock,
Clock，
ah,
ah，
clock.
clock。
October,
October，
ah, October.
ah，October。
Soft,
Soft，
ah,
ah，
soft.
soft。