In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to pronounce the EH as in BED vowel.
我们将学习如何发音像在单词BED中的EH元音。
To make this sound,
要发出这个声音，
the jaw drops, EH,
下巴下垂，EH，
and the tongue remains forward with the tip touching lightly behind the bottom front teeth.
舌头保持向前，舌尖轻轻触碰下前牙的后面。
EH.
EH。
The mid-front part of the tongue lifts a little bit towards the roof of the mouth,
舌头的中前部稍微抬起，靠近上颚，
while the back of the tongue feels like it stretches wide.
而舌头的后部感觉像是向两侧伸展。
EH.
EH。
In a stressed syllable,
在重读音节中，
the voice has a little curve up,
声音有一个小的上扬曲线，
then curve down.
然后下降。
EH.
EH。
It's stressed in the word said.
在单词said中是重读的。
Let's watch up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观看。
The jaw drops,
下巴下垂，
the tongue tip touches the back of the bottom front teeth,
舌尖触碰下前牙的后面，
and the middle part arches up towards the roof of the mouth.
中部向上拱起靠近上颚。
Said.
Said。
EH.
EH。
Said.
Said。
In an unstressed syllable,
在非重读音节中，
the vowel is lower and flatter in pitch,
元音的音调更低更平，
as well as quieter and quicker.
而且更安静更快。
EH.
EH。
The vowel is unstressed in the word employ.
在单词employ中元音是非重读的。
EH.
EH。
Let's take a look up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观看。
Relaxed jaw drop.
放松的下巴下垂。
The middle part of the tongue arches up towards the roof of the mouth.
舌头的中部向上拱起靠近上颚。
Here we compare the stressed EH from said on top, with the stressed EH from said on top.
这里我们比较单词said中重读的EH在上面，和单词said中重读的EH在上面。
Notice the jaw drops more for the stressed version of this vowel.
注意在这个元音的重读版本中下巴下垂得更多。
Because the unstressed version of the vowel is shorter,
因为元音的非重读版本更短，
there isn't enough time to make the full jaw drop.
没有足够的时间让下巴完全下垂。
EH, stressed.
EH，重读。
Said.
Said。
EH.
EH。
EH, unstressed.
EH，非重读。
Employ.
Employ。
EH.
EH。
EH,
EH，
EH.
EH。
EH,
EH，
EH.
EH。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Red.
Red。
EH.
EH。
Red.
Red。
Never.
Never。
EH.
EH。
Never.
Never。
Embrace.
Embrace。
EH.
EH。
Embrace.
Embrace。
Enter.
Enter。
EH.
EH。
Enter.
Enter。
Embody.
Embody。
EH.
EH。
Embody.
Embody。
Desk.
Desk。
EH.
EH。
Desk.
Desk。