In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to make the M consonant sound.
我们将学习如何发出 M 辅音的声音。
This sound is simply made by pressing the lips together lightly,
这个声音只需轻轻地将双唇合拢，
mm,
嗯，
while making a sound with the vocal cords.
同时用声带发声。
So this is a voiced consonant,
所以这是一个浊辅音，
mm.
嗯。
The teeth may begin to part a little in preparation for the next sound,
牙齿可能会稍微分开，为下一个声音做准备，
mm,
嗯，
which will pull the lips a little bit,
这会稍微拉动双唇，
mm.
嗯。
Because the soft palate is lowered,
因为软腭降低，
air comes up through the nasal passages.
空气通过鼻腔流出。
This makes it a nasal consonant.
这使得它成为一个鼻音辅音。
You can feel the vibration in your nose,
你可以在鼻子里感受到振动，
mm.
嗯。
There are only three nasal sounds in American English,
美式英语中只有三个鼻音，
mm,
嗯，
mm.
嗯。
Let's look at this sound up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个声音。
The word mom.
单词 mom。
Lips press together as the jaw drops a little bit.
双唇合拢，颌部稍微下垂。
Another M at the end.
结尾处的另一个 M。
Lips press together.
双唇合拢。
Summer.
单词 summer。
Lips press together.
双唇合拢。
The M consonant.
M 辅音。
Mom.
Mom。
Summer.
Summer。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Make,
Make，
mm,
嗯，
make.
make。
My,
My，
mm,
嗯，
my.
my。
Forming, mm,
Forming，嗯，
forming.
forming。
Dim,
Dim，
mm,
嗯，
dim.
dim。
Mistake, mm,
Mistake，嗯，
mistake.
mistake。