In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to go over how to pronounce the F and V consonants.
我们将学习如何发F和V这两个辅音。
These two sounds are paired together because they take the same mouth position.
这两个音被放在一起是因为它们的口型相同。
Fff is unvoiced, meaning only air passes through the mouth,
Fff是清音，意味着只有气流通过口腔，
and Vvv is voiced,
而Vvv是浊音，
meaning you make a sound with the vocal cords.
意味着你需要用声带发声。
Vvv.
Vvv。
To make these sounds,
要发出这些音，
the bottom lip lifts and touches the very bottom of the top front teeth.
下唇抬起并接触上门牙的最底部。
Fff, Vvv.
Fff, Vvv。
The top lip lifts a little bit to get out of the way of the bottom lip.
上唇稍微抬起以让出下唇的空间。
You don't want to see your bottom lip disappear.
你不希望看到下唇消失。
Fff.
Fff。
It's actually the inside of the lip, here,
实际上是唇的内侧，
that makes contact with the teeth.
与牙齿接触。
Fff,
Fff，
Vvv.
Vvv。
The tongue should stay relaxed so the air can easily push through,
舌头应保持放松，以便气流轻松通过，
causing the bottom lip to vibrate against the top teeth.
使下唇在上牙上振动。
Let's look at the sounds up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这些音。
The top lip lifts so the bottom lip has room to vibrate against the bottom of the top front teeth.
上唇抬起，以便下唇有空间在上门牙的底部振动。
Very.
Very。
Bottom lip goes to the bottom of the top front teeth.
下唇接触上门牙的底部。
Flavor.
Flavor。
The bottom lip goes to the top front teeth for the F,
下唇接触上门牙发F音，
and again for the V.
然后再发V音。
Enough.
Enough。
Bottom lip to top front teeth.
下唇接触上门牙。
When you work on these consonants and words with these consonants,
当你练习这些辅音和含有这些辅音的单词时，
watch yourself and make sure your bottom lip doesn't curl in.
观察自己，确保下唇没有卷进去。
Fff, Vvv.
Fff, Vvv。
Remember, it's the inside of the lip that makes these sounds.
记住，是唇的内侧发出这些音。
The F and V consonants.
F和V辅音。
Very.
Very。
Flavor.
Flavor。
Enough.
Enough。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Live.
Live。
Vvv.
Vvv。
Live.
Live。
Value.
Value。
Vvv.
Vvv。
Value.
Value。
Provide.
Provide。
Vvv.
Vvv。
Provide.
Provide。
Fresh.
Fresh。
Fff.
Fff。
Fresh.
Fresh。
Offer.
Offer。
Fff.
Fff。
Offer.
Offer。
Tough.
Tough。
Fff.
Fff。
Tough.
Tough。