In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to make the S and Z consonant sounds.
我们将学习如何发 S 和 Z 辅音音。
These two sounds are paired together because they take the same mouth position.
这两个音被放在一起是因为它们的口型相同。
Sss is unvoiced, meaning only air passes through the mouth.
Sss 是无声的，意味着只有空气通过口腔。
And Zzz is voiced,
而 Zzz 是有声的，
meaning you make a sound with the vocal cords.
意味着你用声带发出声音。
Zzz.
Zzz。
To make the sounds,
要发出这些音，
the lips part and the corners pull back a little while the teeth themselves lightly touch.
嘴唇分开，嘴角稍微向后拉，同时牙齿轻轻接触。
Sss.
Sss。
Zzz.
Zzz。
There are two ways to make these sounds.
有两种方法可以发出这些音。
One,
一种，
with the tip of the tongue down,
舌尖向下，
lightly touching the back of the bottom front teeth.
轻轻接触下前牙的后面。
Or,
或者，
by pointing the tip of the tongue up.
将舌尖向上指。
You may find that the position of the tongue tip depends on the sounds around the S and Z.
你可能会发现舌尖的位置取决于 S 和 Z 周围的音。
Let's look at these sounds up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这些音。
The teeth lightly touch,
牙齿轻轻接触，
tongue tip is down,
舌尖向下，
and you can see a lot of the tongue through the teeth.
你可以通过牙齿看到很多舌头。
Sip.
Sip。
Again, teeth lightly touch, the tongue tip is pointed down.
再一次，牙齿轻轻接触，舌尖向下。
Miss.
Miss。
The tongue tip stays down as the teeth come together.
当牙齿合拢时，舌尖保持向下。
Fizz.
Fizz。
This time, you'll see the tongue tip point up before the teeth close.
这次，你会看到舌尖在牙齿合拢前向上指。
And up.
向上。
The S and Z sounds.
S 和 Z 音。
Sip.
Sip。
Miss.
Miss。
Fizz.
Fizz。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Note,
注意，
the letter S can make the Z sound.
字母 S 可以发出 Z 音。
Some.
Some。
Ss.
Ss。
Some.
Some。
Must.
Must。
Ss.
Ss。
Must.
Must。
Less.
Less。
Ss.
Ss。
Less.
Less。
Zip.
Zip。
Zzz.
Zzz。
Zip.
Zip。
Cousin.
Cousin。
Zzz.
Zzz。
Cousin.
Cousin。
Easy.
Easy。
Zzz.
Zzz。
Easy.
Easy。